{
    "laila_show_2025_07_14": {
        "name": "Laila Show July 17, 2025",
        "questions": [
            {
                "id": "q1",
                "question": "What do I do with my hands?????",
                "choices": [
                    "A) I don't know",
                    "B) I don't know",
                    "C) I don't know",
                    "D) I don't know"
                ],
                "correctAnswer": 2
            },
            {
                "id": "q2",
                "question": "Break glass in case of emergency.",
                "choices": [
                    "A) That's not a question",
                    "B)  ",
                    "C) Why is B blank?",
                    "D) All of the above"
                ],
                "correctAnswer": 3
            },
            {
                "id": "q3",
                "question": "Laila Smith is a _______",
                "choices": [
                    "A) 100%",
                    "B) Text me when you get home",
                    "C) Is this something I should be worried about?",
                    "D) Mathematicians cry too"
                ],
                "correctAnswer": 3
            },
            {
                "id": "q4",
                "question": "What's the most important thing about me?",
                "choices": [
                    "A) I do my best!",
                    "B) I DO MY BEST !!!!!!!",
                    "C) IDODO OD M$Y BESTSETST",
                    "D) DONT TOUCH ME"
                ],
                "correctAnswer": 1
            },
            {
                "id": "q5",
                "question": "Where are are we right now?",
                "choices": [
                    "A) I WAS BORN IN THIS CLUB",
                    "B) Right now is all we have, do what you want to do, we're in the club and we're staying. Also if you're in the club, you're doing now or before. ",
                    "C) Third answer.",
                    "D) Fourth answer."
                ],
                "correctAnswer": 1
            },
            {
                "id": "q6",
                "question": "What is Laila's nickname?",
                "choices": [
                    "A) Li",
                    "B) Sweet Grammy ",
                    "C) Big Hoss",
                    "D) if I told you that I'd have to kill you"
                ],
                "correctAnswer": 1
            }
        ]
    },
    "random_fun_facts": {
        "name": "Random Fun Facts",
        "questions": [
            {
                "id": "rf1",
                "question": "What percentage of the ocean have humans explored?",
                "choices": [
                    "A) 5%",
                    "B) 20%",
                    "C) 50%",
                    "D) We're still looking for it"
                ],
                "correctAnswer": 0
            },
            {
                "id": "rf2",
                "question": "How many times can you fold a piece of paper in half?",
                "choices": [
                    "A) 4 times",
                    "B) 7 times",
                    "C) 12 times",
                    "D) Until your patience runs out"
                ],
                "correctAnswer": 1
            },
            {
                "id": "rf3",
                "question": "What's the most abundant gas in Earth's atmosphere?",
                "choices": [
                    "A) Oxygen",
                    "B) Carbon dioxide",
                    "C) Nitrogen",
                    "D) Hot air from politicians"
                ],
                "correctAnswer": 2
            }
        ]
    },
    "tech_humor": {
        "name": "Tech Humor",
        "questions": [
            {
                "id": "th1",
                "question": "What's the hardest part of programming?",
                "choices": [
                    "A) Writing the code",
                    "B) Debugging the code",
                    "C) Naming things",
                    "D) Explaining to non-programmers what you do"
                ],
                "correctAnswer": 2
            },
            {
                "id": "th2",
                "question": "How do you tell if someone uses Arch Linux?",
                "choices": [
                    "A) They have superior skills",
                    "B) They tell you",
                    "C) They complain about Ubuntu",
                    "D) They haven't showered in days"
                ],
                "correctAnswer": 1
            },
            {
                "id": "th3",
                "question": "What's the difference between a programmer and a user?",
                "choices": [
                    "A) Programmers create bugs, users find them",
                    "B) Programmers drink more coffee",
                    "C) Users actually read documentation",
                    "D) There is no difference, both ignore error messages"
                ],
                "correctAnswer": 3
            }
        ]
    },
    "maddie_cmon_everybody_2025_07_14": {
        "name": "Maddie Cmon Everybody July 14 2025",
        "questions": [
            {
                "id": "q1",
                "question": "C'mon _______",
                "choices": [
                    "A) Nobody",
                    "B) Somebody",
                    "C) Everybody",
                    "D) Bodyody"
                ],
                "correctAnswer": 3
            },
            {
                "id": "q2",
                "question": "Damn yall is maddie killing it right now or what",
                "choices": [
                    "A) Omg no",
                    "B) Omg yes",
                    "C) asvns4a8f8s4fnsajfnkasdj",
                    "D) yes"
                ],
                "correctAnswer": 2
            }
        ]


    }
}